[{"entity_name": "CHARLES DICKENS", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Author who wrote A Christmas Carol"}, {"entity_name": "PETER CRATCHIT", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Bob Cratchit's son"}, {"entity_name": "BOB CRATCHIT", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "BOB CRATCHIT was a clerk who worked for Ebenezer Scrooge. He was also known to have gone down the Cornhill slide. \n"}, {"entity_name": "TINY TIM", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Bob Cratchit's son, referred to as \"Tiny Tim\""}, {"entity_name": "EBENEZER SCROOGE", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Ebenezer Scrooge, the surviving partner of the firm of Scrooge and Marley, was a grasping, covetous old man. On Christmas Eve, he was visited by three ghosts who showed him the errors of his ways. \n"}, {"entity_name": "TIM CRATCHIT", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Youngest son of Bob Cratchit"}, {"entity_name": "MR. FEZZIWIG", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Kindhearted and jovial old merchant"}, {"entity_name": "FRED", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Fred is Scrooge's nephew. \n"}, {"entity_name": "GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PAST", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Phantom showing things past"}, {"entity_name": "GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Spirit of a kind, generous, and hearty nature"}, {"entity_name": "GHOST OF CHRISTMAS YET TO COME", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Apparition showing the shadows of things which yet may happen"}, {"entity_name": "GHOST OF JACOB MARLEY", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Specter of Scrooge's former partner in business"}, {"entity_name": "JOE", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Marine-store dealer and receiver of stolen goods"}, {"entity_name": "MR. TOPPER", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "A bachelor"}, {"entity_name": "DICK WILKINS", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "A fellow apprentice of Scrooge's"}, {"entity_name": "BELLE", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "A comely matron, an old sweetheart of Scrooge's"}, {"entity_name": "CAROLINE", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Wife of one of Scrooge's debtors"}, {"entity_name": "MRS. CRATCHIT", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Wife of Bob Cratchit"}, {"entity_name": "BELINDA CRATCHIT", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Daughter of Bob and Mrs. Cratchit"}, {"entity_name": "MARTHA CRATCHIT", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Daughter of Bob and Mrs. Cratchit"}, {"entity_name": "MRS. DILBER", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "A laundress"}, {"entity_name": "FAN", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "The sister of Scrooge"}, {"entity_name": "MRS. FEZZIWIG", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "The worthy partner of Mr. Fezziwig"}, {"source_entity": "BELINDA CRATCHIT", "target_entity": "MRS. CRATCHIT", "description": "Belinda Cratchit is the daughter of Mrs. Cratchit"}, {"source_entity": "MARTHA CRATCHIT", "target_entity": "MRS. CRATCHIT", "description": "Martha Cratchit is the daughter of Mrs. Cratchit"}, {"source_entity": "TIM CRATCHIT", "target_entity": "MRS. CRATCHIT", "description": "Tim Cratchit is the son of Mrs. Cratchit"}, {"source_entity": "TIM CRATCHIT", "target_entity": "BOB CRATCHIT", "description": "Tim Cratchit is the son of Bob Cratchit"}, {"source_entity": "BELINDA CRATCHIT", "target_entity": "BOB CRATCHIT", "description": "Belinda Cratchit is the daughter of Bob Cratchit"}, {"source_entity": "MARTHA CRATCHIT", "target_entity": "BOB CRATCHIT", "description": "Martha Cratchit is the daughter of Bob Cratchit"}, {"entity_name": "SCROOGE", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Ebenezer Scrooge is the main character of the story. He is a miserly and ill-tempered businessman who is against the holiday Christmas. Scrooge was Marley's business partner and sole executor. He is a stingy and unfeeling employer who barks precise instructions to Cratchit and then leaves for the day. He is visited by three spirits on Christmas Eve, including the ghost of his former business partner, Jacob Marley.  Scrooge is a greedy and miserly old man who is visited by three spirits on Christmas Eve. \n"}, {"entity_name": "MARLEY", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Jacob Marley was Ebenezer Scrooge's former business partner. He died seven years prior to the events of the story. Marley's ghost visits Scrooge on Christmas Eve. \n"}, {"entity_name": "TIM", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Tim is Bob Cratchit's crippled son"}, {"entity_name": "'CHANGE", "entity_type": "EVENT", "description": "'Change is a place where Scrooge rings money and is known to be good at it"}, {"entity_name": "HAMLET", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Hamlet's father died before the play started"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "MARLEY", "description": "Scrooge and Marley were business partners for many years. Marley died seven years ago and Scrooge became the sole executor of Marley's will.  Some people who were new to the business mistakenly referred to Scrooge as \"Marley\". \n"}, {"entity_name": "CHRISTMAS EVE", "entity_type": "EVENT", "description": "Christmas Eve is the day before Christmas. In the story, the Three Spirits visit Scrooge on Christmas Eve. \n"}, {"entity_name": "CITY", "entity_type": "GEO", "description": "The location where Scrooge lives"}, {"entity_name": "SCROOGE'S NEPHEW", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Scrooge's nephew is Scrooge's relative who celebrates Christmas. He visits Scrooge on Christmas Eve and invites him to dinner. Scrooge's nephew is in favor of celebrating the holiday Christmas. \n"}, {"entity_name": "CHRISTMAS", "entity_type": "EVENT", "description": "Christmas is an annual holiday that Scrooge dreads.  It is a Christian holiday that Scrooge does not enjoy.  Scrooge's nephew wants to celebrate Christmas, but Scrooge has different views on the holiday. \n"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "CHRISTMAS", "description": "Scrooge hates the holiday Christmas and believes there is no reason to celebrate it"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "SCROOGE'S NEPHEW", "description": "Scrooge's nephew loves Christmas and wants his uncle to celebrate with him"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE'S NEPHEW", "target_entity": "CHRISTMAS", "description": "Scrooge's nephew enjoys Christmas, while Scrooge does not. Despite Scrooge's aversion to the holiday, his nephew celebrates Christmas with enthusiasm. \n"}, {"entity_name": "UNCLE", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Scrooge is Scrooge's nephew's uncle, and they do not see eye-to-eye on Christmas"}, {"entity_name": "CLERK", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "The clerk is an employee of Scrooge who greets Scrooge's nephew warmly. When the nephew praises Christmas, the clerk cheers and is reprimanded by Scrooge for it. \n"}, {"entity_name": "PARLIAMENT", "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION", "description": "A legislative branch of government that Scrooge's nephew is suggested to join"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE'S NEPHEW", "target_entity": "UNCLE", "description": "Scrooge's nephew is related to Scrooge as his uncle"}, {"source_entity": "UNCLE", "target_entity": "CHRISTMAS", "description": "Scrooge and his nephew disagree about how Christmas is celebrated"}, {"source_entity": "CLERK", "target_entity": "SCROOGE", "description": "The clerk works for Scrooge and is Scrooge's employee. \n"}, {"source_entity": "CLERK", "target_entity": "CHRISTMAS", "description": "The clerk cheers after Scrooge's nephew praises Christmas"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE'S NEPHEW", "target_entity": "PARLIAMENT", "description": "Scrooge suggests that his nephew would be a good politician"}, {"entity_name": "TWO GENTLEMEN", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Two men who visit Scrooge on Christmas Eve to collect donations for the poor"}, {"entity_name": "MR. MARLEY", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Scrooge's former business partner who died seven years ago"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE'S NEPHEW", "target_entity": "SCROOGE", "description": "Scrooge's nephew is Scrooge's relative"}, {"source_entity": "TWO GENTLEMEN", "target_entity": "SCROOGE", "description": "The two gentlemen visit Scrooge to collect donations for the poor"}, {"source_entity": "MR. MARLEY", "target_entity": "SCROOGE", "description": "Mr. Marley was Scrooge's business partner"}, {"entity_name": "CHRISTIAN", "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION", "description": "A group of people who follow the teachings of Jesus Christ"}, {"entity_name": "POOR", "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION", "description": "People who are in need of financial assistance"}, {"entity_name": "CHRISTIAN CHEER", "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION", "description": "A group of people who are trying to help the poor"}, {"entity_name": "SURPLUS POPULATION", "entity_type": "GEO", "description": "A group of people who are not needed or wanted"}, {"entity_name": "GOTHIC WINDOW", "entity_type": "GEO", "description": "A type of window that is found in Gothic architecture"}, {"entity_name": "LABOURERS", "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION", "description": "People who do physical labor"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "POOR", "description": "Scrooge believes that the poor should go to the workhouse or die"}, {"source_entity": "CHRISTIAN CHEER", "target_entity": "POOR", "description": "The Christian Cheer is a group of people who are trying to help the poor by providing them with food and warmth"}, {"entity_name": "LORD MAYOR", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "The Lord Mayor of London celebrated Christmas"}, {"entity_name": "LORD MAYOR'S HOUSEHOLD", "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION", "description": "The Lord Mayor's household celebrated Christmas"}, {"entity_name": "BOBS CRATCHIT", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Bob was out on a slide at the end of Cornhill"}, {"source_entity": "LORD MAYOR", "target_entity": "LORD MAYOR'S HOUSEHOLD", "description": "The Lord Mayor's household reported to the Lord Mayor"}, {"source_entity": "LORD MAYOR", "target_entity": "BOBS CRATCHIT", "description": "Bob Cratchit worked for the Lord Mayor"}, {"entity_name": "CAMDEN TOWN", "entity_type": "GEO", "description": "Town that Cratchit lives in"}, {"entity_name": "CORNHILL", "entity_type": "GEO", "description": "Street which Cratchit slides down"}, {"entity_name": "CITY OF LONDON", "entity_type": "GEO", "description": "Financial district of London"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "BOB CRATCHIT", "description": "Scrooge is Bob Cratchit's employer"}, {"source_entity": "BOB CRATCHIT", "target_entity": "CAMDEN TOWN", "description": "Bob Cratchit lives in Camden Town"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "CITY OF LONDON", "description": "Scrooge works in the financial district of London"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "CHRISTMAS EVE", "description": "The story takes place on Christmas Eve"}, {"entity_name": "MARLEY'S GHOST", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "The ghost of Marley, who visits Scrooge on Christmas Eve."}, {"entity_name": "JACOB", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Business partner of Ebenezer Scrooge"}, {"source_entity": "JACOB", "target_entity": "EBENEZER SCROOGE", "description": "Jacob was a business partner of Ebenezer Scrooge"}, {"entity_name": "GHOST", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "The Ghost of Jacob Marley is the first spirit to visit Scrooge."}, {"entity_name": "THREE SPIRITS", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "The Three Spirits are three spirits that visit Scrooge on Christmas Eve."}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "GHOST", "description": "Scrooge is visited by the Ghost of Jacob Marley on Christmas Eve"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "THREE SPIRITS", "description": "Scrooge is visited by the Three Spirits on Christmas Eve"}, {"source_entity": "GHOST", "target_entity": "THREE SPIRITS", "description": "The Ghost of Jacob Marley is one of the Three Spirits that visit Scrooge on Christmas Eve"}, {"source_entity": "THREE SPIRITS", "target_entity": "CHRISTMAS EVE", "description": "The Three Spirits visit Scrooge on Christmas Eve"}, {"entity_name": "PHANTASMS", "entity_type": "PERSON", "description": "Spirits that visit Scrooge on Christmas Eve"}, {"source_entity": "MARLEY", "target_entity": "PHANTASMS", "description": "Marley is a spirit, like the other phantoms that Scrooge sees"}, {"source_entity": "SCROOGE", "target_entity": "PHANTASMS", "description": "Scrooge sees the phantoms as they visit his home on Christmas Eve"}]